Is it written in my fate to see only buffalo dung
and father's washed clothes,
right? Because finally I and my
group are leaving, come
[song voice] My dear, Ganisa, did you
understand, that is why I have taken out the box from the top of the cupboard and
started packing. I do
n't have any clothes, you know girls, with
great difficulty I got two kurtis,
those too were loose, now I will have to fit this one. Now the
machine is not working, so I will have to stitch it with needle and thread,
but before that, as usual, I
wash my face thoroughly and then
wear this viral D10 mask.
It does not contain any harmful chemicals to remove tanning.
Now by the time this dries,
my kurti will also be stitched.  Look,
after two stitches the kurti fit perfectly.  Now let me
wash this.  Wow, what a great
result.  That's why I use this face wash daily.
And if
you also want to remove tan, then this mask is a great combo.  If you
use it, tanning will completely disappear.
I have tagged this combo.
Also, if you want the link then comment the link.
Hey, what are you saying.  My friend also came.
Picking up the jhinta bag and look at Buddhu Dev ji and Mota
Bhai, they are polishing the car. So,
after polishing the car and keeping the jhinta bag aside,
taking the blessings of the elders, we have set off
on our new trip. Radhe-Radhe ji.